No brother, the new event that is 100% sure to produce Big Red is finally online!
If you find such a treasure map in the dam, you can go to the corresponding location and open the small treasure chest Big Red. However,
The location of this treasure chest is super underworld! Some brothers stood in the middle of the West and still couldn't find where the treasure chest was.
Then Xiao Pu is here to show everyone the twelve treasure chest locations in the dam. Everyone, hurry up and collect them!
Treasure Box No. 1 is behind this box under the dam, go to the place where you knocked the fish bridge before;
Treasure chest No. 2 is under the small tower on the south side of the cement wall; treasure chest No. 3 is on the shelf standing in the pipe.
The image is almost out of the map; treasure box No. 4 is on the box behind the visitor center;
Treasure chest No. 5 is next to the field supplies box in this container on the river beach.
Treasure chest No. 6 is in this shed outside Xiao Ji Ning.
Treasure Chest No. 7 is behind this container on the top road of Seven Hegemons. Then there is the fattest treasure chest No. 8,
Next to this medical pile in the container area. The items given in this treasure chest will only turn red. Xiao Gu,
I just took two out from here in the afternoon, and they made a lot of money. Treasure chest No. 9 is next to Ji Ning.
Do you think this circle is at the top? In fact, it is hidden in the small crevice behind the box below.
Give me Golden Horn and Red Warm. Treasure chest No. 10 is not even in the circle drawn in the image.
But in this corner next to the pickup truck. Treasure chest No. 11 is very hidden.
Inside this cement pipe outside the administration building. Treasure chest No. 12 is not on the river bank shown on the map either.
But inside the cement wall, hidden behind this sandbag.
There are always a lot of locations for all the treasure chests, so everyone should collect them first and wait until they touch the treasure map before looking at them.
If Big Red is opened, remember to tell Xiao Pu. OK? You said you couldn't touch the treasure map at all,
Then why do you think I'm squatting here? 大红 Of course, it’s to rob someone else’s money box.
If you are added as a friend by someone, just don’t send Xiaopu out.